

Arda ERBAHARLI

Nationality: Turkish | **Email address:** <u>ardaerbaharli1@gmail.com</u> | **Website:**

https://ardaerbaharli.github.io | LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/arda-erbaharli-5401471aa/ | **Github:**

https://github.com/ardaerbaharli/ Portfolio:

https://ardaerbaharli.github.io/portfolio/ Address: Ankara, Türkiye (Home)

ABOUT ME

I have been actively engaged in software development for over four years, specializing in the creation of mobile games using the C# programming language and Unity. Over the past three years, my primary focus has been on game development, allowing me to gain extensive experience in this field. Since December 2021, I have been working as a freelance game developer, collaborating on numerous projects including various genres, primarily targeting mobile platforms.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/12/2021 - CURRENT

FREELANCE GAME DEVELOPER UPWORK

As a Top Rated Plus Freelance Game Developer at Upwork, I've been collaborating on numerous projects across the world, primarily targeting mobile platforms. I've worked on hyper casual, puzzle, educational, endless runners, trivia, card games and many more.

15/08/2022 - 12/09/2022 Ankara, Türkiye

GAME DEVELOPER INTERN ARD GRUP

I have developed 3 hyper-casual game clones.

- <u>Globo Run</u> (https://ardaerbaharli.github.io/portfolio#globoRun) => This is a 3D endless runner game where the player tries to avoid obstacles whilst the player speed increase
- <u>Helix Jump</u> (https://ardaerbaharli.github.io/portfolio/small-games#helixJump)=> Clone of the popular game Helix Jump.
- <u>Arrow Throw (https://ardaerbaharli.github.io/portfolio/small-games#arrowThrow)</u> => Clone of the popular game Easter Egg Toss.

31/05/2021 - 27/06/2021 Ankara, Türkiye

GAME DEVELOPER INTERN ARD BILISIM

I have developed a classic Solitaire game with Unity from scratch. You can see here (https://ardaerbaharli.github.io/portfolio#solitaire). Also helped with the implementation of a 3rd party package.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

22/09/2018 - 06/07/2023 Ankara, Türkiye

COMPUTER ENGINNER Başkent University

Website www.baskent.edu.tr

01/12/2022 - 01/06/2023

GAME DEVELOPMENT TRAINEE Google Oyun ve Uygulama Akademisi

Website https://oyunveuygulamaakademisi.com

TRAINEE Panteon

Website https://www.panteon.games/akademi/

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **TURKISH**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C1	C1	B2	B2	C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Tools & Technology

.NET Framework | Version Control System (Git) | Adobe Photoshop | .NET Core | Git | Unity

Programming Languages

C#